<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>music on Miranda Zhang&#39;s Website</title>
        <link>https://example.com/tags/music/</link>
        <description>Recent content in music on Miranda Zhang&#39;s Website</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 16 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.com/tags/music/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>first attempt at positive focusing</title>
        <link>https://example.com/p/positive-focusing/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://example.com/p/positive-focusing/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;listening to &amp;rsquo;everything goes on&amp;rsquo; &amp;amp; unexpectedly felt a pang of awe + bliss. tried to focus on this (literally, i spent ~5 mins reading about focusing, which made it harder to access the feeling RIP) and i&amp;rsquo;m not sure if i&amp;rsquo;m &amp;lsquo;doing it right&amp;rsquo; but potential things of note&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;✨ &lt;strong&gt;i am deeply moved by a combination of beautiful images &amp;amp; sound:&lt;/strong&gt; it was important that i watched the music video, i think, because the video plays in the background of my mind when i hear this song. but it&amp;rsquo;s not like i really remember the video; it&amp;rsquo;s more that i remember the colours (the BEAUTIFUL vibrancy that reminds one of Kyoto Animation) &amp;amp; the crispness &amp;amp; the emotional valence of the story&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;✨ &lt;strong&gt;transience &amp;amp; renewal &amp;amp; liminality is really beautiful to me:&lt;/strong&gt; scenes of loss that are bittersweet / tinged with regeneration (this video, Anohana, Cloud Atlas, Hyouka) are my favourite pieces of media. i also really enjoy sunrises and NYE for similar reasons - you know it&amp;rsquo;s going to be over, but at least it&amp;rsquo;s beautiful right now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;this seems like a good thing to lean into because i&amp;rsquo;m actually very scared of change. like, i now feel confused about why i find transience so aesthetically pleasing despite being so unable to handle it in real life?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;things to try&lt;/h2&gt;
☑️ seek out more media with these vibes (and don&#39;t feel bad for consuming it!)
&lt;br&gt;
☑️ writing about personal loss from a narrator&#39;s point-of-view / imbuing my own experiences with main-character-energy + romance 
&lt;br&gt;
☑️ find good sunrise places!!!!!!!!!!! how have i not seen a sunrise ONCE here</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
