<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>Posts on Miranda Zhang&#39;s Website</title>
        <link>https://example.com/post/</link>
        <description>Recent content in Posts on Miranda Zhang&#39;s Website</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>Realizing I just justified the past hour at a social as &#39;for impact,&#39; but didn&#39;t realize it because I didn&#39;t literally think about impact (I was thinking, &amp;quot;you can help people!&amp;quot;) Agh. But now I&#39;m aware, next time I&#39;ll give greater weight to following what seems exciting and frivolous.</title>
        <link>https://example.com/p/socialising-for-impact/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://example.com/p/socialising-for-impact/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;context:&lt;/strong&gt; As part of my burnout recovery, I&amp;rsquo;m avoiding using &amp;ldquo;impact&amp;rdquo; as a justification for my actions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Realizing I just justified the past hour at a social as &amp;lsquo;for impact,&amp;rsquo; but didn&amp;rsquo;t realize it because I didn&amp;rsquo;t literally think about impact (I was thinking, &amp;ldquo;you can help people!&amp;rdquo;)
Agh. But now I&amp;rsquo;m aware, next time I&amp;rsquo;ll give greater weight to following what seems exciting and frivolous.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Starting to think the way through imposter syndrome blocking further thought/writing is, &amp;quot;just do it anyway.&amp;quot;</title>
        <link>https://example.com/p/do-it-anyway/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://example.com/p/do-it-anyway/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Starting to think the way through imposter syndrome blocking further thought/writing is, &amp;ldquo;just do it anyway.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Don&amp;rsquo;t know enough? Maybe that&amp;rsquo;s true, but just do it anyway. There&amp;rsquo;s probably no harm, and lots of benefit, in writing up thoughts and getting feedback.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;It&amp;rsquo;s also useful that I&amp;rsquo;m realizing that this behaviour, and related thoughts such as &amp;ldquo;this is somebody else&amp;rsquo;s job; how can I produce anything valuable when they work on it full-time?&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;I don&amp;rsquo;t know enough to say anything worthy&amp;rdquo; is a form of imposter syndrome!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Related post that I love:&lt;/strong&gt; &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://web.archive.org/web/20220316125646/http://www.katwoods.co/home/there-are-no-walls&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;There are no walls&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Three updates on my burnout</title>
        <link>https://example.com/p/three-updates-on-my-burnout/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 22 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://example.com/p/three-updates-on-my-burnout/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Note: One fourth, general update is that burnout is ill-defined and very individual, so I wouldn&amp;rsquo;t want you to apply any of my takeaways to your own situation unless you understand my context and resonate strongly.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I talked about burnout with my new therapist and, oh boy, it&amp;rsquo;s really reinforcing my perception that so much of the value from therapy comes from noticing and questioning things-you-might-be-getting-wrong. Here are three ways I updated today:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;should-is-shorthand-for-strategic&#34;&gt;Should is shorthand for strategic&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TL;DR:&lt;/strong&gt; When I say I &amp;lsquo;should&amp;rsquo; be doing, all I&amp;rsquo;m doing is positing a hypothesis. It doesn&amp;rsquo;t justify beating myself up for not doing something I think I &amp;lsquo;should,&amp;rsquo; because it&amp;rsquo;s not an obligation or value judgment. I&amp;rsquo;m simply choosing which experiments I want to run right now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve been saying that I &amp;lsquo;should&amp;rsquo; take a full break: go on a vacation, stop seeing EAs, go on a road trip. But what does this even mean?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Emotionally, it means I feel guilty because I don&amp;rsquo;t think I&amp;rsquo;m doing what is best. But in this context, applying a judgment like &amp;ldquo;best&amp;rdquo; is only useful if it points me towards the most effective way to recover from burnout. So when I say I &amp;lsquo;should&amp;rsquo; take a full break, I am claiming that taking a full break would be strategically optimal for&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Energizing me&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Imbuing my life with a sense of regular &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Joie_de_vivre&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;joie de vivre&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Raising my baseline mood&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;All of these are testable! So when I say &amp;lsquo;should,&amp;rsquo; I&amp;rsquo;m really making a claim (positing a hypothesis) that can be confirmed or falsified.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I will also say something like, I &amp;lsquo;shouldn&amp;rsquo;t&amp;rsquo; be upskilling or talking about EA. Yet, sometimes, those things also&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Energize me&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Raise my mood&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Imbue my life with a sense of excitement and wonder&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;So guess what—things that I &amp;lsquo;shouldn&amp;rsquo;t&amp;rsquo; do provide evidence for what may be strategically better/worse for me. Why &lt;em&gt;shouldn&amp;rsquo;t&lt;/em&gt; I do these things, then? Because people who have no access to my internal experience recommended something different for burnout recovery?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Similarly, when I say I &amp;lsquo;should&amp;rsquo; be trying lots of different activities to find an energizing hobby, I&amp;rsquo;m positing that an energizing hobby will be crucial for my burnout recovery. When my therapist questioned this, I broke a little (in a good way). What do you mean, maybe I don&amp;rsquo;t &lt;strong&gt;need&lt;/strong&gt; to find a consistently atelic hobby to recover?&lt;sup id=&#34;fnref:1&#34;&gt;&lt;a href=&#34;#fn:1&#34; class=&#34;footnote-ref&#34; role=&#34;doc-noteref&#34;&gt;1&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/sup&gt; Maybe—alternative hypothesis—becoming energized is more about my mindset than whatever I&amp;rsquo;m doing?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Finally, nowhere does saying &amp;lsquo;should&amp;rsquo; break down into&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I am obligated to do this&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;It is moral to do this&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I am failing if I am not doing this&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Rather, &amp;lsquo;should&amp;rsquo; just represents the claim I hold the most credence in at the moment.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;exploration--excitement-is-an-orientation&#34;&gt;Exploration &amp;amp; excitement is an orientation&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;TL;DR:&lt;/strong&gt; As a meditation guru might say—it&amp;rsquo;s all about your mind. Maybe I can &lt;em&gt;make&lt;/em&gt; activities exciting, rather than finding exciting activities?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;Searching&lt;/em&gt; has been a theme throughout the past month (even after my job search), as I&amp;rsquo;ve been seeking adventure and excitement and freedom! Let&amp;rsquo;s call what I&amp;rsquo;ve been seeking, &amp;ldquo;zest for life&amp;rdquo; (what I consider the English version of &lt;em&gt;joie de vivre&lt;/em&gt;). Naturally, this brings to mind escapist fantasies of going on a road trip, skydiving, or just taking a complete break.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;One hypothesis is that exciting activities are what generate a zest for life.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Another hypothesis is that my mindset is what generates a zest for life, such that I can find a sense of exploration and excitement in many ordinary activities, like chilling with my friends or &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://example.com/p/positive-focusing/&#34; &gt;listening to music&lt;/a&gt;.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m not sure which is more accurate, but I hadn&amp;rsquo;t even considered the latter as a possibility. My therapist questioning whether I necessarily had to find a hobby to recover from burnout, however, has opened up a new approach that I&amp;rsquo;m excited about. What if the core issue is my mindset, such that (a) I might not find a reliably energizing activity until I address my attitude &amp;amp; (b) I might not need a reliably energizing &lt;em&gt;activity,&lt;/em&gt; because I can turn anything into this with the right mindset?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Based on my previous therapeutic experiences, this direction seems promising.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;embracing-irresponsibility-is-the-key-to-my-burnout&#34;&gt;[Embracing] Irresponsibility is the key to my burnout&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;TL;DR:&lt;/b&gt; I want to feel gleeful about not doing what I &amp;lsquo;should&amp;rsquo; be doing and/or what the average person is doing.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For the past month, I&amp;rsquo;ve felt sheepish about my efforts to address my burnout. Specifically, I would feel insecure and ashamed when I was asked, &amp;ldquo;What are you doing?&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Me:&lt;/b&gt; &amp;ldquo;Trying to recover from burnout.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;b&gt;Them:&lt;/b&gt; &#34;What are you doing to recover?&#34;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;i&gt;Me, internally: Wow, they can&#39;t find out that I have no idea, because then they might think I&#39;m dumb/not serious/incompetent/un-strategic etc. And that would reflect poorly on me, and my commitment to this community, and my impact.&lt;/i&gt;
&lt;br&gt;&lt;B&gt;Me:&lt;/b&gt; Oh, I&#39;m doing a pretty bad job. I&#39;m generally just chilling and ... trying a bunch of activities to see if I can find a hobby I reliably enjoy... 
&lt;/blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The funny thing is, I would still express loads of uncertainty and confusion—I wasn&amp;rsquo;t really trying to hide it, but I would feel down on myself for feeling this way. My therapist suggested that I assume that others are by default critical, which does seem accurate.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But even if people are, or even if I come across someone who is more critical than average, I should embrace what I&amp;rsquo;m doing nevertheless. I call this embracing &lt;em&gt;irresponsibility:&lt;/em&gt; who cares if other people think I&amp;rsquo;m doing fuck-all? Let them be confused! Let them be judgemental! It doesn&amp;rsquo;t change that I&amp;rsquo;m leading my life the best way I think I can.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;ve only really tapped into this sense of irreverence once before—when I was rejected from all but one of the T20s to which I applied. Interestingly, that also came with a sense of shame and failure—I was just able to get over that and feel defiance, instead. I&amp;rsquo;m not sure how to tap into this again, but I suspect I can brute-force it with enough practice!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;div class=&#34;footnotes&#34; role=&#34;doc-endnotes&#34;&gt;
&lt;hr&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li id=&#34;fn:1&#34;&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I still think &amp;lsquo;find a reliable hobby&amp;rsquo; is a good hypothesis, but I feel less justified in getting down on myself for not making enough progress on this. Maybe not making progress is just a sign that my hypothesis was wrong!&amp;#160;&lt;a href=&#34;#fnref:1&#34; class=&#34;footnote-backref&#34; role=&#34;doc-backlink&#34;&gt;&amp;#x21a9;&amp;#xfe0e;&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;/div&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>My current hypothesis for an emotional processing workflow that works for me</title>
        <link>https://example.com/p/july-emotional-workflow/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://example.com/p/july-emotional-workflow/</guid>
        <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;carve-out-time-to-process&#34;&gt;Carve out time to process.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Someday, I&amp;rsquo;ll be able to do this faster. But right now, it takes me like 10-15 minutes to deeply dive into what I&amp;rsquo;m feeling, and I think this is really productive lol&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;name-acknowledge-and-accept-the-feeling&#34;&gt;Name, acknowledge, and accept the feeling.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;e.g., &amp;ldquo;Wow, this news makes me feel really bad. But why? Oh &amp;hellip; Probably because I feel envy. But what is it about envy that feels bad? Oh - it&amp;rsquo;s because envy leads to self-deprecation and comparison, where you think you aren&amp;rsquo;t &amp;ldquo;enough.&amp;rdquo; And this makes you sad.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Something about naming the feeling helps me get to the associated thoughts. For some reason, I often feel like I don&amp;rsquo;t &lt;em&gt;have&lt;/em&gt; immediate negative thoughts because it&amp;rsquo;s so hard for me to &amp;lsquo;hear&amp;rsquo; them. But it&amp;rsquo;s easier for me to identify, I think, when I hit upon the emotion.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Focusing on being curious so I can identify the emotion is also a great way to avoid judging myself! Judging myself is a surefire way to keep feeling awful (e.g., &amp;ldquo;wow, you can&amp;rsquo;t even be happy for them or feel grateful for what you have?&amp;rdquo;)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;come-up-with-alternate-frames-or-compassionate-thoughts&#34;&gt;Come up with alternate frames or compassionate thoughts.&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Very much in the style of, &amp;lsquo;what would you say to a friend?&amp;rsquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the past, this step has felt way too effortful for me, to the point where I thought CBT was just less effective for me than DBT or radical acceptance. But I think I actually &lt;em&gt;can&lt;/em&gt; do CBT effectively - I just need to first get to a less emotionally-activated place, and then sometimes I hit upon a framing that REALLY works.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;e.g., &amp;ldquo;You are not as smart or competent&amp;rdquo; ➡️ &amp;ldquo;oh man, you are smart and competent in so many ways. And so is X! … Just because you didn’t get this one job doesn’t mean you’re not as smart or as competent. It just means you have different skills. And having different skills is great, because we need all kinds of people to help solve the world’s problems.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Wow, did that framing ever work! I have reaffirmed my value, and I am now able to fully embrace the pride I feel for X and nudge my envy into a quiet appreciation for their gifts + striving to learn from them.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;figure-out-some-way-to-remember-the-techniques-that-work-for-me&#34;&gt;Figure out some way to remember the techniques that work for me&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;still working on this :( I log things on Notion/Facebook/my website but I really feel wish I had a better memory lol. Maybe I should start making flashcards.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>On treating oneself with curiosity and compassion</title>
        <link>https://example.com/p/treating-oneself-with-curiosity-and-compassion/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 19 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://example.com/p/treating-oneself-with-curiosity-and-compassion/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;On Facebook, I wondered whether anyone &lt;em&gt;actually&lt;/em&gt; defaulted to treating themselves with curiosity / compassion after a mistake? E.g., thinking &amp;ldquo;Great, I&amp;rsquo;m learning more about myself and how to improve!&amp;rdquo; vs &amp;ldquo;Wow, I suck at this.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;My friend Nikola Jurkovic had some wonderful insights into how to lean into the former framing:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;on-framing-mistakes-as-learning&#34;&gt;On framing mistakes as learning&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I personally don&amp;rsquo;t suffer much from beating myself up over mistakes and it&amp;rsquo;s mostly because I don&amp;rsquo;t really think &amp;ldquo;mistake&amp;rdquo; is that coherent of a concept. there are input-output pairs to how the world behaves, and sometimes I badly predict how certain imputs correspond to certain outputs, and then I can be like &amp;ldquo;oh, I guess that doesn&amp;rsquo;t work that way”&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;for instance a few weeks ago I was super sleepy and having the last conversation of the day with some people and I made a comment that was slightly snarky/insulting to one of the people I was talking to, and I was like &amp;ldquo;fuck I just made a mistake and I feel bad and I&amp;rsquo;m bad&amp;rdquo; for a moment until I caught the feeling and started thinking about it the normal way of &lt;strong&gt;&amp;ldquo;is this a sign I have to set up better internal systems or was this a bet I&amp;rsquo;d take again?”&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2 id=&#34;achieving-this-mindset&#34;&gt;Achieving this mindset&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;internalizing-determinismno-free-will-and-human-fallibility&#34;&gt;internalizing determinism/no free will and human fallibility.&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m almost never angry at other people because I see everything, including other people, mostly as physical systems going through timesteps.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;A cup dropped from shoulder height will fall and shatter when it hits the ground. Water in a pot will boil when a fire is lit under it. Everything is reducible to simple physical processes, and there isn&amp;rsquo;t a point on the cup-human spectrum where I&amp;rsquo;m like &amp;ldquo;ah, that&amp;rsquo;s complex enough, now I can get angry at it!&amp;rdquo;. It makes no sense to be angry at a cup for shattering when it hits the ground - it did what cups do when they hit the ground.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Similarly, it makes no sense to be angry at a human doing something wrong - it did what humans sometimes do. Keep in mind that here I&amp;rsquo;m not advocating never feeling the emotion of anger. I&amp;rsquo;m saying that on some platonic level, there&amp;rsquo;s nothing bad or wrong about following the laws of physics.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think it&amp;rsquo;s probably good to feel anger some of the time, but noone &amp;ldquo;deserves&amp;rdquo; to be angry at. There are probably ways to feel anger while also not directing it towards specific people. Most of the anger I feel is vaguely towards the universe dealing us a bad deck. But it&amp;rsquo;s not anger at others, it&amp;rsquo;s anger &lt;strong&gt;with&lt;/strong&gt; others, similar to the distinction of laughing at someone vs laughing &lt;strong&gt;with&lt;/strong&gt; someone.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;When someone does something &amp;ldquo;wrong&amp;rdquo; to hurt me, &lt;strong&gt;the thought that&amp;rsquo;s going through my mind is mostly &amp;ldquo;it sucks that the universe is like this, that people can get hurt for no good reason, and I will punch the universe until no-one is ever hurt again&amp;rdquo;. Not because the universe &amp;ldquo;deserves&amp;rdquo; to be punched, but because I want to punch things and the universe just so happens not to feel pain when punched (by &amp;ldquo;punch the universe&amp;rdquo; i mostly mean &amp;ldquo;change the world with determination&amp;rdquo;)&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;cultivating-loving-kindness-towards-myself-and-towards-others&#34;&gt;cultivating loving kindness towards myself and towards others&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m not sure how determinist buddhism is generally, but in it there&amp;rsquo;s this very nice idea that basically, everyone is looking for happiness. Everyone is trying to make their corner of the universe a little bit better, but some people are confused or hurt, and in their confusion and pain, hurt others and themselves in trying to do this. I think that this is abstractly very close to the truth, but there are some exceptions, such as sadists, but sadists are victims of their own preferences being unaligned with others, which they too didn&amp;rsquo;t choose.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think this insight is also true very often on a smaller level. I&amp;rsquo;ve found that most of the time people snap at me in anger, they are undergoing high amount of physical pain in that moment. They might be very tired, they might have a piercing headache or toothache, they might be suffering from a disease. People who are suffering are much more likely to be angry than those who are not.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;From this perspective, when someone snaps angrily at me, I don&amp;rsquo;t really feel hurt that much, I&amp;rsquo;m mostly thinking &amp;ldquo;this person is very likely in a lot of pain right now, and I wonder what caused that, and what I can do to help them&amp;rdquo;.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;pointing-mental-habits-inwards-how-would-you-treat-others&#34;&gt;pointing mental habits inwards: how would you treat others?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In therapy there is a very useful technique used in many different approaches, and that is judging oneself similarly to how one judges others (of course, having the foundation of not judging others harshly).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Many people can beat themselves up for mistakes they made as children, but when described a different child who made the same mistakes, feel nothing but compassion and sorrow for the child.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The crucial step here is realizing that there is nothing about you being you that makes your mistakes bigger than other people&amp;rsquo;s mistakes. You&amp;rsquo;re just like other people: half-monkey-half-god, and the monkey half is very often confused and hurt, and makes mistakes in its confusion and pain.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;you-are-just-a-physical-system-what-is-the-best-way-to-make-yourself-run-smoothly&#34;&gt;you are just a physical system. what is the best way to make yourself run smoothly?&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And so, when you bring it all together, you are a physical system that follows the laws of physics, half-monkey-half-god, that has certain parts which aren&amp;rsquo;t used to the world, and there&amp;rsquo;s no difference between you and other people that&amp;rsquo;d make your mistakes bigger than others.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;In this framing, you could imagine someone else living your life, making the same mistakes, and you&amp;rsquo;re tasked with taking care of them and making sure they thrive. How would you talk to them? What advice would you give them? Would you yell at them? Show them love and compassion? The answer to these questions should dictate how you actually treat yourself internally&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h3 id=&#34;see-everything-as-a-bet&#34;&gt;see everything as a bet&lt;/h3&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Connected to determinism is the mindset of seeing everything as a bet. You bet on how specific actions will lead to specific outcomes, and sometimes, they don&amp;rsquo;t. But, as with any other bets, sometimes people lose bets that are worth taking, and sometimes people win bets that aren&amp;rsquo;t worth taking. Instead of looking at the outcome of the bet itself, I think it&amp;rsquo;s better to focus most of our attention of the information we had while taking on the bet.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For instance, sometimes telling the truth bites me in the ass, but I don&amp;rsquo;t beat myself up when this happens. This is not because I place some innate value on telling the truth, but because I realized long ago that telling the truth is on average more useful than not doing it. There are times that this will bite me in the ass, but it&amp;rsquo;s a bet I&amp;rsquo;d  take again, as on average, it has been useful&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think another thing useful in internalizing determinism/ the laws of physics/ everything being a bet, is that when you take a high EV bet that results in you losing, then you basically took the punch for all the parallel universe yous that won. The actual truth value of this statement is debatable because map != territory and many worlds may not be true, but on a higher level this is a useful abstraction&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Noticing that my incredible gratitude/surprise at people in my life helping me overcome problems might signal that, on the flip side, I&#39;m not well-calibrated on how tractable problems are and/or am easily dissuaded by problems. </title>
        <link>https://example.com/p/calibrated-on-problems/</link>
        <pubDate>Mon, 18 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://example.com/p/calibrated-on-problems/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Noticing that my incredible gratitude/surprise at people in my life helping me overcome problems might signal that, on the flip side, I&amp;rsquo;m not well-calibrated on how tractable problems are and/or am easily dissuaded by problems.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;E.g., I had considered one solution that involved someone helping me, but dismissed it as too implausible. When I talked about my problem with the person, they raised the exact same solution I&amp;rsquo;d come up with - the one I thought would&amp;rsquo;ve been too ludicrous to ask for!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;Examples of behaviours I want to do more of instead&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ignore the first time the thought, &amp;ldquo;this is too hard, let&amp;rsquo;s give up&amp;rdquo; comes up&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Ask for things directly (bottleneck: social cost. Solution: find socially charismatic ways of posing requests? Maybe something like, &amp;ldquo;would it be absurd to ask for &amp;hellip;?&amp;rdquo;)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;When faced with a problem I have no idea how to solve, set a 5 minute timer and brainstorm wildly. Then ask a friend.&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Generically adopting a policy of, &amp;ldquo;anything is solvable if you try hard enough!&amp;rdquo; (It&amp;rsquo;s just about the trade offs you&amp;rsquo;re willing to make)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>first attempt at positive focusing</title>
        <link>https://example.com/p/positive-focusing/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 16 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://example.com/p/positive-focusing/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;listening to &amp;rsquo;everything goes on&amp;rsquo; &amp;amp; unexpectedly felt a pang of awe + bliss. tried to focus on this (literally, i spent ~5 mins reading about focusing, which made it harder to access the feeling RIP) and i&amp;rsquo;m not sure if i&amp;rsquo;m &amp;lsquo;doing it right&amp;rsquo; but potential things of note&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;✨ &lt;strong&gt;i am deeply moved by a combination of beautiful images &amp;amp; sound:&lt;/strong&gt; it was important that i watched the music video, i think, because the video plays in the background of my mind when i hear this song. but it&amp;rsquo;s not like i really remember the video; it&amp;rsquo;s more that i remember the colours (the BEAUTIFUL vibrancy that reminds one of Kyoto Animation) &amp;amp; the crispness &amp;amp; the emotional valence of the story&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;✨ &lt;strong&gt;transience &amp;amp; renewal &amp;amp; liminality is really beautiful to me:&lt;/strong&gt; scenes of loss that are bittersweet / tinged with regeneration (this video, Anohana, Cloud Atlas, Hyouka) are my favourite pieces of media. i also really enjoy sunrises and NYE for similar reasons - you know it&amp;rsquo;s going to be over, but at least it&amp;rsquo;s beautiful right now.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;this seems like a good thing to lean into because i&amp;rsquo;m actually very scared of change. like, i now feel confused about why i find transience so aesthetically pleasing despite being so unable to handle it in real life?&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;h2&gt;things to try&lt;/h2&gt;
☑️ seek out more media with these vibes (and don&#39;t feel bad for consuming it!)
&lt;br&gt;
☑️ writing about personal loss from a narrator&#39;s point-of-view / imbuing my own experiences with main-character-energy + romance 
&lt;br&gt;
☑️ find good sunrise places!!!!!!!!!!! how have i not seen a sunrise ONCE here</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>My cup overfloweth: I am beyond grateful to the EA community, which has *continuously* exceeded my expectations.</title>
        <link>https://example.com/p/my-cup-overfloweth/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://example.com/p/my-cup-overfloweth/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;My cup overfloweth ☕ Beyond grateful to the EA community, which has &lt;em&gt;continuously&lt;/em&gt; exceeded my expectations. Acquaintances and friends alike have supported me emotionally, logistically, and financially, enabling me to keep pursuing what I think are the likeliest paths for me to have the most positive impact.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Is this partly due to EA&amp;rsquo;s unusually high trust in its community? If so, this is yet another special thing I want to preserve about EA.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The other part, I&amp;rsquo;m sure, comes from how EA attracts some of the world&amp;rsquo;s most kind, intelligent, &amp;amp; driven people. 🥰&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>AI generated art &#43; misc. happy reflections</title>
        <link>https://example.com/p/ai-generated-art/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://example.com/p/ai-generated-art/</guid>
        <description>&lt;img src="https://example.com/img--post/ai%20generated%20art.jpg" alt="Featured image of post AI generated art &#43; misc. happy reflections" /&gt;&lt;h2 id=&#34;misc-happy-reflections-below&#34;&gt;misc happy reflections below&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Treated myself to a coffee tasting and feeling much more optimistic about addressing my burnout.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I think the thing I&amp;rsquo;m missing is &amp;lsquo;zest for life,&amp;rsquo; or some feeling beyond obligation. This helps me understand the finding that taking a vacation might not sustainably treat burnout - vacations might help with rediscovering the feeling, but if you can&amp;rsquo;t find ways to insert pockets of joy into your normal life, then it&amp;rsquo;s back to square one.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Hopefully, this means that my current plan of staying in my normal but really trying to find atelic activities will bear fruit. If I can find pockets of joy here while I&amp;rsquo;m &lt;em&gt;not&lt;/em&gt; working, then I can carry those over when I do start working here.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Feeling surprisingly energized by AI discussion, but mainly when (a) I&#39;m successfully learning (so this is not a signal about the domain), (b) evaluating AI safety stories (maybe a sign I should trial strategy fit?), (c)  talking to my friends (I am extremely suspicious of this convergence and would bet on this leading me to overestimate the impact of these discussions)</title>
        <link>https://example.com/p/energized-by-ai/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://example.com/p/energized-by-ai/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Feeling surprisingly energized by AI discussion, but&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;mainly when I&amp;rsquo;m successfully learning (so this is not a signal about the domain)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;when evaluating AI safety stories (maybe a sign I should trial strategy fit?)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;when talking to my friends (I am extremely suspicious of this convergence and would bet on this leading me to overestimate the impact of these discussions)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Bay Area Wishlist</title>
        <link>https://example.com/p/bay-area-wishlist/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 12 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://example.com/p/bay-area-wishlist/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I have a &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1CQwZ-XOcRDBXu1ZI6F_BwAj6q4ZjbLl8icndcpbMpwM/edit?usp=sharing&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;GDoc with things-I-want-to-do in the Bay Area&lt;/a&gt;! I would be excited to do these with friends, so please see if you&amp;rsquo;d be interested in joining me to do any of these!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1CQwZ-XOcRDBXu1ZI6F_BwAj6q4ZjbLl8icndcpbMpwM/edit?usp=sharing&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1CQwZ-XOcRDBXu1ZI6F_BwAj6q4ZjbLl8icndcpbMpwM/edit?usp=sharing&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(context below)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;~ request for collective hivemind thoughts ~&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m worried about how best to address my burnout before my OPT unemployment ends in mid-August and I would appreciate suggestions for any of the below approaches&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;In one month, make a really concerted effort to tackle my burn-out. This may include&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;going on a short nature retreat (is there some way I can do this for ~free?)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;doing Focusing (who can teach me?)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;cuddle sessions (I should probably schedule these)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;going nuclear (i.e., withdraw from EA for the month)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;ol start=&#34;2&#34;&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Leave the US until I&amp;rsquo;m ready to work&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ol&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Really undesirable because I like the people and environment here! Possibly mitigated if I can actually come up with things I&amp;rsquo;d be excited to do. Less likely: staying with my parents. More likely: staying with my friends&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Soooo is there anyone who&amp;rsquo;d be willing to let me stay at theirs for ~.5-1 month? I imagine the UK is going to be the likeliest candidate&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Feedback update (yes, I take these seriously!)</title>
        <link>https://example.com/p/feedback-akash/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://example.com/p/feedback-akash/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;EDIT:&lt;/strong&gt; Thinking about some feedback I got on the doc and I want to taboo &amp;ldquo;impact&amp;rdquo; as a justification. Unless I&amp;rsquo;m joking, if I say I want to do something for &amp;ldquo;impact&amp;rdquo; and don&amp;rsquo;t provide a theory of change for the action, if you point this out to me then I will give you $5. This will hold until January 1, 2023.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Someone told me that they were confused why I was moving to Oakland &amp;amp; that living there (instead of Berkeley) was going to bottleneck my impact.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;To clarify both why I&amp;rsquo;m moving to Oakland and how I&amp;rsquo;m thinking around the impact rationale behind my move to the Bay Area, I wrote up &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://docs.google.com/document/d/1v01pkjl0mwyHkd_K9udnRj3MGJhSySt_UXjWhpgYeao/edit?usp=drivesdk&amp;amp;fbclid=IwAR3tsZJ4YUl-kdMPplbOwfCxm1m0FT1pR-GVseSQ3ucZVDSFfr90XYfr2X0&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;this doc&lt;/a&gt; (per their suggestion).&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also, y&amp;rsquo;all, I&amp;rsquo;m disappointed that this is the most critical thing I&amp;rsquo;ve received. If something is preventing you from leaving me critical feedback, let me know anonymously! Let&amp;rsquo;s fix this!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(FWIW, I think a stronger criticism emerges from this feedback that I got, which is something like - &amp;ldquo;right now, you&amp;rsquo;re not a good enough community builder to be impactful. This could be resolved if you lived in Berkeley.&amp;rdquo; I would be interested in further exploring this, if I got feedback on why I&amp;rsquo;m not a good enough community builder)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>pivoted from testing technical research fit to reading about s-risks and I&#39;m pleasantly surprised by the fact that, for the first time in a bit, I&#39;m actually keen to spend my day ~ working ~ (e.g., I&#39;m bothered by distractions and want to turn my notifications off)</title>
        <link>https://example.com/p/pivot/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://example.com/p/pivot/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;pivoted from testing technical research fit to reading about s-risks and I&amp;rsquo;m pleasantly surprised by the fact that, for the first time in a bit, I&amp;rsquo;m actually keen to spend my day ~ working ~ (e.g., I&amp;rsquo;m bothered by distractions and want to turn my notifications off)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(definitely still testing fit - have scheduled something for next sunday, and might still do some AIS stuff today!)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Want to test your fit for AI technical safety research with me?</title>
        <link>https://example.com/p/aistr/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://example.com/p/aistr/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m open to a variety of options, whether a couple hours over several days or a weekend &amp;lsquo;retreat!&amp;rsquo; (I&amp;rsquo;m kind of psyched about the retreat option, which is probably just crashing a group house)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I keep saying that &amp;lsquo;I should (and will) test my fit for AI technical research,&amp;rsquo; but actually doing this seems increasingly aversive. So, here&amp;rsquo;s an open call to my non-technical (and technical, if you enjoy watching your friend(s) struggle) friends to spend a day testing our fits for AISTR!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I was thinking we could try finding solutions for ELK or follow Holden Karnofsky&amp;rsquo;s advice in this post: &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://forum.effectivealtruism.org/.../important&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;https://forum.effectivealtruism.org/.../important&lt;/a&gt;&amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(context: me having blocked out the entire day to do this, and feeling worried I&amp;rsquo;m going to give up halfway through)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Doing chores in the morning is one of the most relaxing experiences for me, but I&#39;m not sure why! Some ideas...</title>
        <link>https://example.com/p/chores/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://example.com/p/chores/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Doing chores in the morning is one of the most relaxing experiences for me, but I&amp;rsquo;m not sure why!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some ideas&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I get to feel productive while playing music / watching something (feels better than just purely relaxing, where I have the background thought that I can&amp;rsquo;t justify relaxing)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Physical work is repetitive, largely thoughtless, and hence relaxing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Feeling very productive in the morning is nice&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Some people&#39;s rest day look like writing personal reflections, gaining emotional insight, and/or brainstorming world-changing ideas.Mine is looking like a lot of HSMTMTS sing-alongs and in an effort to not judge myself for it, I&#39;m going to just be really into this!</title>
        <link>https://example.com/p/rest-days/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://example.com/p/rest-days/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Some people&amp;rsquo;s &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://forum.effectivealtruism.org/posts/NDszJWMsdLCB4MNoy/burnout-what-is-it-and-how-to-treat-it?commentId=87ue5WzwaFDbGpcA7&amp;amp;fbclid=IwAR23AGfwOmTPiw1E52u4pBjYm7LGUIgwqkUma2WDjed1XnFlordZ8uzMskQ&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;rest day&lt;/a&gt; look like writing personal reflections, gaining emotional insight, and/or brainstorming world-changing ideas.Mine is looking like a lot of HSMTMTS sing-alongs and in an effort to not judge myself for it, I&amp;rsquo;m going to just be really into this!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Apparently my resting state is singing really badly and not producing impact, and this is totally fine.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Thoughts on &#39;Less often discussed EA emotional patterns&#39;</title>
        <link>https://example.com/p/less-often-discussed-ea-emotional-patterns/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://example.com/p/less-often-discussed-ea-emotional-patterns/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;I love &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://forum.effectivealtruism.org/posts/gHuYfvB3ALhjTd4SQ/less-often-discussed-ea-emotional-patterns?fbclid=IwAR1piUPpYKTkXemmsfzbsB22Aers-L8om7O8U7WwFCT92stm2gXtaxREJxc&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;this Forum post&lt;/a&gt;. It captures a significant portion of my reflections on EA x mental health in the past 6 months.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Choice quotes&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&amp;ldquo;But sometimes, doing altruistic things means doing something you don’t feel like doing. If working on your mental health seems like a daunting task you would rather avoid because spending your time working on EA things feels more urgent, other’s needs seem more important than your own, sacrificing yourself for others feels better than spending any effort on yourself – then spending significant effort to get better could actually be the best action for you right now.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&amp;ldquo;I sometimes notice myself telling me that I am just too stupid and passive to ever get an impactful job in an EA hub, because it is somehow easier to think that instead of admitting that I just really don’t want to move to an EA hub (or anywhere from where I currently live). This is probably because I somehow think it is better to be stupid than selfish, or maybe it is because some part of me believes that I cannot fix stupidity, but I should be able to become more altruistic&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;“In a way, the fact that I donate regularly is a justification to keep on living, because each month I’m alive, I keep producing positive value.”&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&amp;ldquo;I think EA is very compelling for people who have trouble believing their lives have intrinsic worth. You cannot prove the intrinsic worth of anything (it is an axiom), but EA can give you a sense of estimating your instrumental worth, like how many lives you have saved by donating. [&amp;hellip;] Ironically, having your impact define your self-worth can actually reduce your impact in multiple ways&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&amp;ldquo;Life is uncertain and making good decisions is difficult. Nobody, not even the EA movement, has a verified, all-encompassing model of the world.
This can be a hard thing to admit especially for people who first became attracted to EA because of the “reason and evidence” part. This was certainly really tempting to me: the world seemed confusing and difficult, and all possible actions to make things right seemed to have downsides; and then, suddenly, a movement that tells me that there are estimates and calculations on what you should do, so if you want to know what to do, you can just look at the numbers and follow the result.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&amp;ldquo;the belief “I’m too stupid to work on AI risk” might be less crushing than “I would probably be able to work on AI risk, but I just don’t want relocate even if I get a job in the field, but also I think I should not mind relocating if it is necessary to work on AI risk because AI risk is super important, and if in 30 years everyone I love dies it’s going to be my fault”. Here, the perceived stupidness is protecting her from feeling ashamed or guilty for having preferences that are not optimized for saving the world.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;&amp;ldquo;Often, working on your mental health is locally a lot harder than sticking to the patterns you have learned. That’s why most people are only motivated to relearn their patterns only when they actually feel really awful.&amp;rdquo;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(personal update: experimenting both with mainstream self-esteem interventions &amp;amp; more mindfulness-inspired abandoning-the-self stuff to work on the entanglement of personal worth w/ impact)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Thought I needed to find some atelic hobbies &amp; it turns out they were what they&#39;ve been all along: card games and musicals.</title>
        <link>https://example.com/p/atelic/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://example.com/p/atelic/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Thought I needed to find some atelic hobbies &amp;amp; it turns out they were what they&amp;rsquo;ve been all along: card games and musicals.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;16-year-old me would be proud.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>processing feedback update: successfully processed some of the most detailed feedback I&#39;ve gotten yet!</title>
        <link>https://example.com/p/processing-feedback/</link>
        <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://example.com/p/processing-feedback/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;processing feedback update: successfully processed some of the most detailed feedback I&amp;rsquo;ve gotten yet!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;things that actively helped:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;imagining being a new homunculus (thanks, Olivia Jimenez!)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;externalizing into action items (thanks, Ari Kagan!)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;contextual things that seem difficult to replicate, but probably helped:&lt;/strong&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I decided on a job, which feels like gain that counterbalances this professional &amp;rsquo;loss&#39;&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I went through several days that felt emotionally worse than this and/or I got some emotional/temporal distance&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>🔈open call for constructive criticism!</title>
        <link>https://example.com/p/criticism/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://example.com/p/criticism/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;em&gt;like a doom circle but anonymous and just for me and not isolated to my impact potential, i guess?&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m trying to stop striving to &amp;ldquo;be the best,&amp;rdquo; and part of that involves learning to take criticism better. So, I&amp;rsquo;m putting out a call to submit (anonymous, if you&amp;rsquo;d like) criticism for me! If this goes well, maybe I&amp;rsquo;ll make this a regular thing. We&amp;rsquo;ll see : )&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;www.admonymous.co/starmz&#34; &gt;Admonymous&lt;/a&gt; | &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;bit.ly/3s1nEA3&#34; &gt;Google Form&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;

</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>y&#39;all thought you knew my ~ vibe ~ but unless you thought my vibe was maisie peters before she blew up, you absolutely Did Not</title>
        <link>https://example.com/p/stay-young/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://example.com/p/stay-young/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;y&amp;rsquo;all thought you knew my ~ vibe ~ but unless you thought my vibe was maisie peters before she blew up, you absolutely Did Not&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(this lyric video is the only thing powering my move-out &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oZU2XaUE1cs&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oZU2XaUE1cs&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
