<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
    <channel>
        <title>thought on Miranda Zhang&#39;s Website</title>
        <link>https://example.com/tags/thought/</link>
        <description>Recent content in thought on Miranda Zhang&#39;s Website</description>
        <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
        <language>en-us</language>
        <lastBuildDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://example.com/tags/thought/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" /><item>
        <title>Realizing I just justified the past hour at a social as &#39;for impact,&#39; but didn&#39;t realize it because I didn&#39;t literally think about impact (I was thinking, &amp;quot;you can help people!&amp;quot;) Agh. But now I&#39;m aware, next time I&#39;ll give greater weight to following what seems exciting and frivolous.</title>
        <link>https://example.com/p/socialising-for-impact/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 26 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://example.com/p/socialising-for-impact/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;&lt;strong&gt;context:&lt;/strong&gt; As part of my burnout recovery, I&amp;rsquo;m avoiding using &amp;ldquo;impact&amp;rdquo; as a justification for my actions.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Realizing I just justified the past hour at a social as &amp;lsquo;for impact,&amp;rsquo; but didn&amp;rsquo;t realize it because I didn&amp;rsquo;t literally think about impact (I was thinking, &amp;ldquo;you can help people!&amp;rdquo;)
Agh. But now I&amp;rsquo;m aware, next time I&amp;rsquo;ll give greater weight to following what seems exciting and frivolous.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>My cup overfloweth: I am beyond grateful to the EA community, which has *continuously* exceeded my expectations.</title>
        <link>https://example.com/p/my-cup-overfloweth/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 15 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://example.com/p/my-cup-overfloweth/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;My cup overfloweth ☕ Beyond grateful to the EA community, which has &lt;em&gt;continuously&lt;/em&gt; exceeded my expectations. Acquaintances and friends alike have supported me emotionally, logistically, and financially, enabling me to keep pursuing what I think are the likeliest paths for me to have the most positive impact.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Is this partly due to EA&amp;rsquo;s unusually high trust in its community? If so, this is yet another special thing I want to preserve about EA.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The other part, I&amp;rsquo;m sure, comes from how EA attracts some of the world&amp;rsquo;s most kind, intelligent, &amp;amp; driven people. 🥰&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Feeling surprisingly energized by AI discussion, but mainly when (a) I&#39;m successfully learning (so this is not a signal about the domain), (b) evaluating AI safety stories (maybe a sign I should trial strategy fit?), (c)  talking to my friends (I am extremely suspicious of this convergence and would bet on this leading me to overestimate the impact of these discussions)</title>
        <link>https://example.com/p/energized-by-ai/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 13 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://example.com/p/energized-by-ai/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Feeling surprisingly energized by AI discussion, but&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;mainly when I&amp;rsquo;m successfully learning (so this is not a signal about the domain)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;when evaluating AI safety stories (maybe a sign I should trial strategy fit?)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;when talking to my friends (I am extremely suspicious of this convergence and would bet on this leading me to overestimate the impact of these discussions)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>pivoted from testing technical research fit to reading about s-risks and I&#39;m pleasantly surprised by the fact that, for the first time in a bit, I&#39;m actually keen to spend my day ~ working ~ (e.g., I&#39;m bothered by distractions and want to turn my notifications off)</title>
        <link>https://example.com/p/pivot/</link>
        <pubDate>Sun, 03 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://example.com/p/pivot/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;pivoted from testing technical research fit to reading about s-risks and I&amp;rsquo;m pleasantly surprised by the fact that, for the first time in a bit, I&amp;rsquo;m actually keen to spend my day ~ working ~ (e.g., I&amp;rsquo;m bothered by distractions and want to turn my notifications off)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(definitely still testing fit - have scheduled something for next sunday, and might still do some AIS stuff today!)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Doing chores in the morning is one of the most relaxing experiences for me, but I&#39;m not sure why! Some ideas...</title>
        <link>https://example.com/p/chores/</link>
        <pubDate>Sat, 02 Jul 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://example.com/p/chores/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Doing chores in the morning is one of the most relaxing experiences for me, but I&amp;rsquo;m not sure why!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Some ideas&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;I get to feel productive while playing music / watching something (feels better than just purely relaxing, where I have the background thought that I can&amp;rsquo;t justify relaxing)&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Physical work is repetitive, largely thoughtless, and hence relaxing&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Feeling very productive in the morning is nice&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;/ul&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Some people&#39;s rest day look like writing personal reflections, gaining emotional insight, and/or brainstorming world-changing ideas.Mine is looking like a lot of HSMTMTS sing-alongs and in an effort to not judge myself for it, I&#39;m going to just be really into this!</title>
        <link>https://example.com/p/rest-days/</link>
        <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://example.com/p/rest-days/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Some people&amp;rsquo;s &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://forum.effectivealtruism.org/posts/NDszJWMsdLCB4MNoy/burnout-what-is-it-and-how-to-treat-it?commentId=87ue5WzwaFDbGpcA7&amp;amp;fbclid=IwAR23AGfwOmTPiw1E52u4pBjYm7LGUIgwqkUma2WDjed1XnFlordZ8uzMskQ&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;rest day&lt;/a&gt; look like writing personal reflections, gaining emotional insight, and/or brainstorming world-changing ideas.Mine is looking like a lot of HSMTMTS sing-alongs and in an effort to not judge myself for it, I&amp;rsquo;m going to just be really into this!&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Apparently my resting state is singing really badly and not producing impact, and this is totally fine.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>Thought I needed to find some atelic hobbies &amp; it turns out they were what they&#39;ve been all along: card games and musicals.</title>
        <link>https://example.com/p/atelic/</link>
        <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://example.com/p/atelic/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Thought I needed to find some atelic hobbies &amp;amp; it turns out they were what they&amp;rsquo;ve been all along: card games and musicals.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;16-year-old me would be proud.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        <item>
        <title>y&#39;all thought you knew my ~ vibe ~ but unless you thought my vibe was maisie peters before she blew up, you absolutely Did Not</title>
        <link>https://example.com/p/stay-young/</link>
        <pubDate>Fri, 10 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
        
        <guid>https://example.com/p/stay-young/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;y&amp;rsquo;all thought you knew my ~ vibe ~ but unless you thought my vibe was maisie peters before she blew up, you absolutely Did Not&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;(this lyric video is the only thing powering my move-out &lt;a class=&#34;link&#34; href=&#34;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oZU2XaUE1cs&#34;  target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;
    &gt;https://www.youtube.com/watch?v=oZU2XaUE1cs&lt;/a&gt;)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        </item>
        
    </channel>
</rss>
